<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BEE</string>
    <string-array name="rules">
        <item>Introduction</item>
        <item>Scoring</item>
        <item>Bonuses</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="description">
        <item>Welcome to BEE, the Drinking Spelling Game! In this game, players take turns either
        telling another player what word they have to spell or spelling said word. The game continues
        until the players decide to end it or the words run out. After inputing all of the player's
        names, the game starts with a random player that holds the phone (known as the Host) with the
        chosen word. He tells the player to his right (the Reader) what the word is, and the Reader
        has a chance to ask the Host what the word's definition is and to hear the word in a sentence.
        </item>
        <item>The Reader attempts to spell the word, and the Host presses whichever button
        determines if the Reader was right or wrong. If the Reader was correct, the Host has to take
        as many sips as the word is worth (the Cost). If the Reader was incorrect, the Reader has to
        take as many sips equal to the word's Cost. The Host then passes the phone to the Reader and
        the new Reader chooses a new word, repeating the cycle until the game ends. All scores must
        be entered manually. After the players unanimously agree to end the game, the current
        Host presses the "End Game" button and the person with the highest score wins.</item>
        <item>In order to spice the game up a bit towards the end and during, there are a handful of
        additional rules and bonuses that the players can decide on using. They are as follows:
        *Final Shot: At the end of the game, the player with the lowest score has to take a shot. If
        there is a tie, tough luck, you're both taking shots.
        *Team Games: If there is an even amount of players, they can break themselves up into two
        teams, with the Host being a random person from Team A and the Reader being a selected person
        from Team B. If the Reader team answers correctly, all members of the Host team have to drink,
        and vice versa for if the Reader team is incorrect. The team with the highest score wins.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
